<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Open Source on Renren Zhang</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1314/tags/open-source/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Open Source on Renren Zhang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.155.3</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:38:45 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1314/tags/open-source/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Stop Treating Your AI Like a Chatbot: The 4 MCP Tools That Gave My Agent a Brain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/ai/recommended_mcp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:38:45 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/ai/recommended_mcp/</guid>
      <description>Explores the limitations of using LLMs as simple chatbots and introduces the Model-Context-Protocol (MCP), detailing four essential tools that provide context, planning, and memory to transform AI into a powerful, autonomous engineering partner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to make your agent smart as openclaw</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/ai/memory-openclaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 02:03:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/ai/memory-openclaw/</guid>
      <description>Provides a practical guide to implementing a persistent memory system for AI coding agents, advocating for a simplified, file-based approach with a manual &amp;lsquo;/save&amp;rsquo; command to capture session context, delivering most of the value with minimal complexity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why This OpenClaw Exploded in a Week</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/ai/openclaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 03:14:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/ai/openclaw/</guid>
      <description>Analyzes the viral success of OpenClaw, an open-source AI assistant that operates locally with OS-level execution, exploring its key innovations like proactive tasks and a decentralized skill ecosystem, while also highlighting its significant security implications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Guide to Starting Open Source in the AI Era</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/career/start_opensource/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:18:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/career/start_opensource/</guid>
      <description>A strategic guide for developers on how to start contributing to open source, from finding the right project and understanding contribution guidelines to making impactful first contributions and leveraging AI tools.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
