<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Renren Zhang</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1314/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Renren Zhang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.155.3</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:38:45 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1314/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Stop Treating Your AI Like a Chatbot: The 4 MCP Tools That Gave My Agent a Brain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/ai/recommended_mcp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:38:45 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/ai/recommended_mcp/</guid>
      <description>Explores the limitations of using LLMs as simple chatbots and introduces the Model-Context-Protocol (MCP), detailing four essential tools that provide context, planning, and memory to transform AI into a powerful, autonomous engineering partner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tools vs. Skills vs. MCP</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/ai/tool_mcp_skill/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:13:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/ai/tool_mcp_skill/</guid>
      <description>Clarifies the distinction between Tools (primitive functions), Skills (complex workflows), and the Model Context Protocol (MCP) in agentic AI, providing an architectural framework for developers to choose the right abstraction for their use case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to make your agent smart as openclaw</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/ai/memory-openclaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 02:03:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/ai/memory-openclaw/</guid>
      <description>Provides a practical guide to implementing a persistent memory system for AI coding agents, advocating for a simplified, file-based approach with a manual &amp;lsquo;/save&amp;rsquo; command to capture session context, delivering most of the value with minimal complexity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Built an iOS App MVP in 4 Hours: A Blueprint for AI-Driven Development</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/tech/ios-vibecoding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 19:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/tech/ios-vibecoding/</guid>
      <description>Outlines a disciplined, four-phase framework for rapidly building a production-ready iOS MVP using an AI assistant, emphasizing rigorous upfront system design, sequenced prompting, and a strict validation loop with atomic Git commits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why This OpenClaw Exploded in a Week</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/ai/openclaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 03:14:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/ai/openclaw/</guid>
      <description>Analyzes the viral success of OpenClaw, an open-source AI assistant that operates locally with OS-level execution, exploring its key innovations like proactive tasks and a decentralized skill ecosystem, while also highlighting its significant security implications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Guide to Starting Open Source in the AI Era</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/career/start_opensource/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:18:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/career/start_opensource/</guid>
      <description>A strategic guide for developers on how to start contributing to open source, from finding the right project and understanding contribution guidelines to making impactful first contributions and leveraging AI tools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>安娜卡列尼娜中的社会评论</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/books/anna_karenina/society_comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:04:46 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/books/anna_karenina/society_comments/</guid>
      <description>A focused look at the social commentary within &amp;lsquo;Anna Karenina,&amp;rsquo; analyzing a key passage on the shifting landscape of 19th-century marriage customs and the inherent conflict between tradition and emerging modernity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>安娜卡列尼娜中的人物描写</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/books/anna_karenina/human_description/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:40:41 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/books/anna_karenina/human_description/</guid>
      <description>A critical analysis of characterization in Tolstoy&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Anna Karenina,&amp;rsquo; examining the nuanced descriptions of Stepan Arkadyich and Levin to reveal themes of social vanity, personal hypocrisy, and authentic human connection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Write a Great Resume</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/career/howtowriteagreatresume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:17:43 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/career/howtowriteagreatresume/</guid>
      <description>Elevate your resume with this strategic guide, focusing on crafting a powerful three-sentence summary, showcasing impact-driven achievements in your work experience, and curating a precise skill set to capture recruiters&amp;rsquo; attention and secure interviews.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
